[{"Qno":1,"Question":"What is SQL Injection?","Option1":"It is a method of writing code using complex encoding methods to ensure the safety &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbspof a database from malicious programs ","Option2":"Uses 64-bit key code to encode the programs","Option3":"It Is a code technique in which malicious SQL statements are inserted into an entry &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbspfield for execution","Option4":"SQL injection may occur due to incorrectly filtered escape characters or incorrect &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsptype handling","Option5":"[A,B]","Option6":"[C,D]","Option7":"null","Answer":"(F) [C,D]"},
{"Qno":2,"Question":"To schedule a maintenance job I need an expression to calculate NEXT SATURDAY AT 20 o'CLOCK (8 PM) no matter when the expression is evaluated.","Option1":"Select trunc(next_day(sysdate,'SA')) + interval '20' hour from dual;","Option2":"Select next_day(sysdate,'SAT') + 20/24 from dual;","Option3":"Select trunc(sysdate,'IW') + 5 + 20/24 from dual;","Option4":"Select trunc(next_day(sysdate,'SATNEXT')) + interval '20' hour from dual;","Option5":"None of the Above","Option6":"null","Option7":"null","Answer":"(D) Select trunc(next_day(sysdate,'SATNEXT')) + interval '20' hour from dual;"},
{"Qno":3,"Question":"What are some of the key features that have helped Exadata to perform better than its conventional database platforms?","Option1":"Smart Cell Scan ","Option2":"Hybrid Columnar Compression ","Option3":"Cache Fusion ","Option4":"Automatic Storage Management","Option5":"[A,B,C,D]","Option6":"[A,B]","Option7":"null","Answer":"(F) [A,B] "},
{"Qno":4,"Question":"What is Oracle Data Redaction?","Option1":"New Feature in Oracle 12c which is part of Oracle Advanced Security ","Option2":"New Feature in Oracle 11g which is part of Oracle Advanced Security","Option3":"Prevents data columns (such as credit card numbers, U.S. Social Security numbers, &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbspand other sensitive or regulated data) from being displayed","Option4":"[A,C]","Option5":"[B,C]","Option6":"null","Option7":"null","Answer":"(D) [A,C]"},
{"Qno":5,"Question":"Which statements about subqueries are true? (Choose three)","Option1":"A single row subquery can retrieve only one column and one row","Option2":"A single row subquery can retrieve only one row but many columns","Option3":"A multiple row subquery can retrieve multiple rows and multiple columns","Option4":"A multiple row subquery can be compared by using the “>” operator","Option5":"A single row subquery can use the IN operator","Option6":"A multiple row subquery can use the “=” operator","Option7":"null","Answer":"[B,C,E]"},
{"Qno":6,"Question":"Which of the following statements most accurately describe Netezza ZoneMaps?","Option1":"ZoneMaps are like indexes, they tell you where specific data is on the disk.","Option2":"ZoneMaps are maintained automatically by the Host.","Option3":" ZoneMaps are like street addresses, they tell Netezza the range of data in a specific &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp extent.","Option4":"ZoneMaps are like statistics and describe the characteristics of stored data.","Option5":"null","Option6":"null","Option7":"null","Answer":"(C) ZoneMaps are like street addresses, they tell Netezza the range of data in a &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbspspecific extent."},
{"Qno":7,"Question":"What is the use of 'APPEND' hint in Oracle?","Option1":"Data is appended to the end of the table, rather than attempting to use existing free &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbspspace within the table.","Option2":"Data is written directly to the data files, by passing through the buffer cache.","Option3":"Referential integrity constraints are maintained","Option4":"Used for SQL transactions to speed up data insertion even for small volume tables","Option5":"null","Option6":"null","Option7":"null","Answer":"(A) Data is appended to the end of the table, rather than attempting to use existing  &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbspfree space within the table."},
{"Qno":8,"Question":"Modifications to the THEATER table are not allowed during the last week in December. When creating a database trigger to enforce this rule, which timing will you use to be most efficient?","Option1":"AFTER","Option2":"WEEKLY","Option3":"BEFORE","Option4":"MONTHLY","Option5":"null","Option6":"null","Option7":"null","Answer":"(C) BEFORE"},
{"Qno":9,"Question":"Which statements describe the state of a package variable after executing the package in which it is declared? (Choose two)","Option1":"It persists across transactions within a session","Option2":"It persists from session to session for the same user","Option3":"It does not persist across transaction within a session","Option4":"It persists from user to user when the package is invoked","Option5":"It does not persist from session to session for the same user","Option6":"null","Option7":"null","Answer":"[A,E]"},
{"Qno":10,"Question":"Which of the statements are true about dependent objects? (Choose three)","Option1":"Invalid objects cannot be described","Option2":"An object with status of invalid cannot be a referenced object","Option3":"The Oracle server automatically records dependencies among objects","Option4":"All schema objects have a status that is recorded in the data dictionary","Option5":"You can view whether an object is valid or invalid in the USER_STATUS data &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbspdictionary view","Option6":"You can view whether an object is valid or invalid in the USER_OBJECTS data &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbspdictionary view","Option7":"null","Answer":"[A,C,F]"},
{"Qno":11,"Question":"What happens when we TRUNCATE from a table?","Option1":"Has an outcome of getting rid of all the rows in a table based on the condition &nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbspspecified irrespective of the constraints on the table","Option2":"It is a DML operation","Option3":"Moves the high water mark and produces few rollback data.","Option4":"Owing to movement of HWM, it takes a long time to complete","Option5":"All of the above","Option6":"null","Option7":"null","Answer":"(C) Move the HWM and produces few rollback"},
{"Qno":12,"Question":"Examine this piece of code.<br>WITH FUNCTION betwnstr (string_in IN VARCHAR2,start_in IN PLS_INTEGER,end_in IN PLS_INTEGER)<br>RETURN VARCHAR2 IS BEGIN<br>RETURN (SUBSTR (string_in,start_in,end_in - start_in + 1));<br>END;<br>SELECT betwnstr (last_name)FROM employees<br>Which of the following is true regarding this code?","Option1":"This SELECT Statement is syntactically correct from 11g upwards","Option2":"This SELECT Statement is syntactically correct from 12c upwards","Option3":"The execution of this statement in 11g will induce context switching","Option4":"The execution of this statement in 12c will prevent context switching","Option5":"All of the above","Option6":"[B,D]","Option7":"[A,C]","Answer":"(F) [B,D]"}]


